myredbook.com 2014-06-06

# Privacy Statement : myredbook

| 

###  Privacy Policy

Effective Date: 1 June 2014   
Last Updated: 1 June 2014 

Sites Covered:: myredbook.com mypinkbook.com mybrownbook.com redslist.com

  * 1\. **GENERAL  
 **
    * 1.1. The operative parties referred to in this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) are myRedBook S.A. d/b/a myredbook.com (hereinafter “RB” or “Company”) and You, the User of this Site.   
 
      * 1.1.1. myRedBook S.A. is the operator of the following Site: myredbook.com . Hereinafter, when first-person pronouns are used in this Policy, (Us, We, Our, Ours, etc.) these provisions are referring to myRedBook S.A. d/b/a the above Site, or as any other Site(s) that We may choose to publish in the future. Additionally, when the terms “the Site” or “Site” are used, these terms refer to any Site published by Us, unless a Site is specifically exempt from this Policy. 
      *  
      * 1.1.2. You, the User – As the User of this Site, this policy will refer to the User as “You” or through any second-person pronouns, such as “Yours,” etc. Hereinafter, the User of the Site shall be referred to in applicable second-person pronouns. 
      *  
    * 1.2. This Policy describes how We use information received about You when You visit Our Site or when You subscribe to, or otherwise use Our online services. This Policy does not cover any information that We may receive from or about You through channels other than through the use of the Site. 
    *  
  * 2\. **REVISIONS TO THIS POLICY** – We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this Policy and Our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. You should periodically check for any modifications of this Policy by re-visiting this page and using the “refresh” button on Your browser. You should note the date of last revision to this Policy, which appears at the top of this Policy. If the “Last Modified” date remains unchanged after You have clicked the “refresh” button on Your browser, You may presume that no changes have been made since the last reading of the Policy. A changed “Last Modified” date indicates that this Policy has been updated or edited, and the updated or edited version supersedes any prior versions immediately upon posting. 
  *  
  * 3\. **PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT** – Visitors to Our Site and services will have multiple manners of interactivity with Us. Depending upon Your level of interaction, We will collect different information about You. The type of information collected is as follows: 
  *  
    * 3.1. Members - Members are those Users who subscribe to Our services. Should You choose to become a Member We will require a name or alias, a valid email address, in the event of membership upgrade or purchase of premium features, credit card information, and any additional information that We, in Our sole discretion, feel is necessary to create a suitable Member account. 
    *  
    * 3.2. Browsers - Browsers are visitors to the Site who typically do not enter into any active data collection pages. Any information gathered from Browsers is also gathered from Members. 
    *  
  * 4\. **HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM YOU**
  *  
    * 4.1. Passive Collection – We passively collect information about You and Your online presence, for example Your current IP address, in order to enhance Your experience on the Site. 
    *  
    * 4.2. Active Collection – We actively collect information from You when You complete the online membership registration form and during purchase of a membership upgrade or premium feature. Please see above Provision 3.1. 
    *  
  * 5\. **HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**
  *  
    * 5.1. The primary use for Your information is to provide You with services You have requested and/or paid for. We also use Your information to deliver customized services to You. Non-personal and aggregate information, such as that collected passively is used in order to improve User experience or to customize the use of Our Site for an aggregate group of customers. 
    *  
    * 5.2. We generally will use Your information for the purposes for which You specifically provide it, for example, to ensure payment for membership upgrade or other services. 
    *  
  * 6\. **SPECIAL CASES** – It is Our policy not to use or share the personal information provided by Browsers or Members in ways unrelated to those described in this Policy without also providing You an opportunity to prohibit such unrelated uses. However, We may disclose personal information about Browsers or Members, or information regarding Your use of the services or websites accessible through Our services, for any reason if, in Our sole discretion, We believe that it is reasonable to do so, including but not limited to the following situations: 
  *  
    * 6.1. To satisfy any laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; 
    *  
    * 6.2. To disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Our Terms and Conditions/User Agreement or other User policies; 
    *  
    * 6.3. To operate Our services properly; 
    *  
    * 6.4. To protect Ourselves, Our Members, and the general public, We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, but only when legally required to do so via a valid subpoena or court order. We specifically reserve the right to disclose any and all information to law enforcement in the event that a crime is committed, is suspected, or if We are compelled to do so by lawful criminal, civil, or administrative process, discovery requests, subpoenas, court orders, writs, or reasonable request of authorities or persons with the reasonable power to obtain such process. We will not cooperate with Governmental administrative or regulatory agencies, private-party litigants, and investigative reporters or journalists regarding disclosure of Your personal information, unless upon Our resistance of such disclosure, We are legally advised to oblige the requesting party. 
    *  
    * 6.5. If We have reason to believe that the User is not the owner of a credit card, even if the credit card use is authorized, We will provide information about You to the credit card holder. We will absolutely provide Your information to the credit card holder if We believe that fraud is a possibility. However, We do not require that there be fraud, as it is Our policy that the credit card holder always has an absolute right to access any and all of Your personal information. 
    *  
    * 6.6. Anyone who violates any of Our designated anti-spam policies may have their personal information made public, at Our discretion. If there is any investigation on any unlawful spamming, or any use of bulk e-mail in order to promote Your User profile, or any use of bulk e-mail in any manner that leads back to Our Site, or any one of Our Sites, We will cooperate with any and all parties completely and freely in order to see that Your bulk e-mail activities stop. 
    *  
  * 7\. **TRANSMITTALS FROM US** – We may send You email communications pertaining to Your activity on the Site, for example, a confirmation email upon membership registration. 
  *  
  * 8\. **FORUMS & MEMBER COMMUNICATION** – Any information or content, personal or otherwise, provided in a post, profile, discussion forum, message board, chat room, Member directory, instant message, or other related service offered by the Site should be considered to be public information. We do not, cannot, and will not act to maintain the privacy of any information that You provide in any such forum or medium of communication. 
  *  
  * 9\. **OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY** – We take various measures to protect the transmission of all sensitive User information. We make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of Our network and systems by storing User data on a secured in-house database wholly separated from any User-accessible directories. Please note that We have no access to Your credit card data as such information is collected by a third party billing agent. We cannot guarantee that Our security measures will prevent third-party ‘hackers’ from illegally obtaining this information. We take all reasonable measures to prevent such breaches of security, but given the resourcefulness of cyber-criminals We are unable to guarantee that Our security is one hundred percent (100%) breach-proof. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite Our reasonable security measures. 
  *  
  * 10\. **HOW TO ACCESS OR MODIFY YOUR INFORMATION** – We offer Our Members the opportunity to access or modify information provided during registration via Your Member profile page. 
  *  
  * 11\. **WHERE TO DIRECT QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY** – If You have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, You may contact Us at  http://www.myredbook.com/support.aspx

|
